https://www.justborn.com/privacy-policy/

Home | Privacy Policy
This site, www.justborn.com, is owned by Just Born, Inc. (“Just Born”).
Just Born’s policy is to respect and protect your privacy. Please read the following to learn about Just Born’s practices with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of information collected online at any of the Web sites owned by Just Born which include www.justborn.com, www.marshmallowpeeps.com, www.mikeandike.com, www.peanutchews.com, www.hottamales.com, www.peepsandcompany.com (the “Just Born Sites”). In addition, please read the Children’s Privacy Policy to learn about how we treat personally identifiable information collected from children under 13 on each Just Born Site.
We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted here. We encourage you to check this page from time to time, because your continued use of a Just Born Site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such changes.
– Domestic U.S. Privacy Statement
– Addendum related to “Canadian Users”
Collection and Use of Information You Provide to Us
Personal Information
We will collect personal information about you, such as your name, e-mail address, and mailing address, when you provide it while on a Just Born Site. You may provide this information when you are registering, redeeming an offer, entering sweepstakes or promotions on a Just Born Site, or when you are otherwise communicating with a Just Born Site. The personal information you provide to a Just Born Site may be combined with information you provide to other Just Born Sites, with demographic and other information that is publicly available, or with other information about you that we may otherwise obtain.
Your personal information is used by Just Born to respond to your requests, tailor offerings to you, fulfill prizes, and communicate with you about products, services, and special offerings offered by Just Born or its marketing partners that may be of interest to you. From time to time, you may receive periodic mailings or emails from Just Born with information on new products or services, special promotions, or other offers from Just Born or its marketing partners. You may opt out of receiving such communications. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our businesses.
We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Just Born Sites or administer activities on our behalf, such as authorization of credit card transactions, order fulfillment and sweepstakes administration. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.
Financial Information
Some Just Born Sites may offer shopping services, member services or other features which request you to provide financial information such as account or credit card numbers.
Just Born will use your financial information to bill you for products and services or otherwise process your transaction. By making a purchase on a Just Born Site, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary to process your transactions. These third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction.
Demographic Information
We may also collect demographic information which you provide to us, such as your zip code, age or income level. We use your demographic information to tailor the Just Born Sites to your interests. We may share demographic information on an aggregate basis with third parties.
Collection and Use of Information Automatically Collected
Internet Protocol
The Just Born Sites automatically collect the Internet Protocol addresses of its visitors. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Just Born Site, track the user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
The Just Born Sites may set and access “cookies” to collect information about how you use the Just Born Sites. This information allows us to customize delivery of information. In addition, on occasion a Just Born Site may also set a “session cookie” to help us administer the Just Born Site. A session cookie expires when you close your browser, and does not retain any information about you after it expires.
Public Forums
Some Just Born Sites may make available chat rooms, forums, and message boards. Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal, financial or other information on any of these forums.
Other Disclosures of Your Information
Sale or Merger
If Just Born is sold to, or merges with, another company not owned by Just Born, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets.
Legal Process
Just Born may disclose your information when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety of Just Born or other visitors to the Just Born Sites.
Opt-Out
We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Just Born. If you do choose to opt-out of such communications, you may:
• Modify your registered user information on the appropriate Just Born Site;
or
• Send an email to consumerrelations@justborn.com.
Access to Personal Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire your personally identifiable information to be contained in our data bank, you can request correction, updating or removal of personal data by e-mailing our Consumer Relations Department. However, these changes may not be effective immediately and may not be retroactive.
Security of Your Personal Information
Your privacy is extremely important to us; we exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your computer to our servers. Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. As soon as we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When you transmit credit card information, we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption.
Links
The Just Born Sites may contain links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those Web sites. When you leave a Just Born Web Site, you should read the privacy policies of each Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
Canadian Users
If you reside in Canada, this notice is intended to comply with the requirements of the federal Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and any substantially similar provincial legislation. The use of the term “personal data” in this privacy policy refers to “personal information” as it is defined in PIPEDA.
Information collected on this site may be stored in, processed in, or accessed from locations outside of Canada, and some or all of these locations may have personal information and privacy laws and standards that are different from those in effect in Canada.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Just Born Site, or your dealings with a Just Born Site, you can contact:
Just Born, Inc.
